ظآزLove's little quiz
takes seven parts sweetظآز
ظآزAnd three parts bitter,
till you and I meetظآز
ظآزI pretend I'm not there,
but secretly stayظآز
ظآزWaiting for youظآز
ظآزWe've got so many
romantic dreams to unfoldظآز
ظآزFinally hearing
the I love you I long to holdظآز
ظآزFalling fast
into the swirl of your eyesظآز
ظآزIt's just too tempting, so temptingظآز
ظآزNever could I have guessedظآز
ظآزMy heart's rhythmظآز
ظآزHow beautiful it is, meeting youظآز
=Late to Love=
(Adapted from "My Husband Is A Billionaire!")
=Episode 13=
Bottom line,
after six months
of tracking NIT-33
and its main metabolite
across different models,
the data strongly suggest
its neuroprotective effect
may be badly flawed
with serious cognitive risks.
Next,
I'll release early findings
on three key areas.
First,
evidence that long-term NIT-33
may trigger
hippocampal inflammation
in animal models.
Mr. Huo,
tech department just found
Dr. X on Deep Diver Forum.
He's running a semi-public stream.
It's about Alzheimer's
drug concerns.
Whatever it takes,
get me
an account that can contact
Dr. X directly.
Understood.
But first,
we need forum access.
Fast-track verification
requires
a verified PhD profile
from a closely related field,
with full public credentials
and a resume.
Tech department is looking now
for a medical PhD
whose identity
can get us inside.
Find Xu Nange. She has a PhD
from Linhai Medical University.
Her profile should work.
Got it.
Seventh and final point.
Confirm whether the metabolite
unexpectedly binds
to key human synaptic proteins.
(Well-designed experiment)
That's all for today's
love lesson.
Class dismissed.
This is my room.
Why are you here?
It's urgent.
Then say it.
I need
your PhD credentials
and certificate number for a forum.
What forum?
A closed professional forum
called Deep Diver.
I have an account.
Just use mine.
Okay. Thanks.
That's all for part one.
From here,
I'll update when I can.
Doubt needs proof.
Change takes courage.
(Deep Diver Forum)
I'm X. See you next time.
Let me take a photo.
Sure.
(Deep Diver Forum)
Hey, Shen Yan.
I left a backend port.
(Good thing I planned ahead.)
(The lecture was prerecorded.)
Three thousand users are online.
Filter by longest watch time.
Got it, Mr. Huo.
Nange.
I forgot
one very important detail.
(No way.)
(Did he see something)
(on my screen?)
Uh...
What detail?
Love Lessons.
What's that?
Love lessons?
Exactly what it sounds like.
Oh? Your research topics
are pretty broad.
Romance too?
I'm a researcher.
I study
all kinds of things.
Besides,
research needs a big sample pool.
Romance is sociology too.
Tell us about your first kiss.
Love Lessons, Episode Four.
Actually, I...
I mean...
you've been in meetings all day.
You must be tired.
Maybe
you should go rest.
Go rest.
Go on.
- You're tired.
- I'm not.
Just go. Go rest.
Sleep early.
Fine.
ظآزCause if you should lose directionظآز
ظآزI hope you make it homeظآز
ظآزCause it's hard to travel aloneظآز
ظآزSo you might as well just take meظآز
ظآزYou might as well have companyظآز
ظآزAnd if you should fall in loveظآز
ظآزIt wouldn't be the worst thingظآز
ظآزCause you wouldn't be the only oneظآز
ظآزThe only oneظآز
ظآزCause it's hard to travel aloneظآز
Xu Nange,
what are you doing?
Why'd you let him kiss you again?
You could've pushed him away.
But I didn't want to.
How could you?
Xu Nange,
are you crazy?
What do I do now?
What...
do you want?
I want to...
clear the air.
Huh? There's no air to clear.
I mean,
I want the truth.
Truth?
What truth?
Xu Nange, are you for real?
I...
I'm real.
You once told me
when the mind is a mess,
brainwaves tell the truth.
So today,
we'll solve this your way.
What do you mean?
Lie test.
No way!
That's like being stripped bare.
We both need answers.
This is the fastest way.
I'll start
with a few easy questions.
Then,
I'll ask one last thing.
Whatever the answer is,
I won't push you again.
Okay.
Is your real name Xu Nange?
Yes.
Brainwaves are steady.
No lie.
You're twenty-eight.
Yes.
You're a PhD student
at Linhai Medical University.
Yes.
Do you like me?
Why'd you stop?
You got
the answer you wanted.
ظآزStand on my own two feetظآز
ظآزHere, I can seeظآز
ظآزEverything that I'm trying to beظآز
I like you too.
ظآزAnd nobody's gonna do it for meظآز
ظآزNo, noظآز
ظآزIf I believe, and I can feelظآز
ظآزIf I can hurt, and I can healظآز
ظآزI'm unbreakableظآز
Xu Nange,
don't run this time.
ظآزIf I believe, and I can feelظآز
ظآزIf I can hurt, and I can healظآز
ظآزI'm unbreakableظآز
ظآزIf I believe, and I can feelظآز
ظآزIf I can hurt, and I can healظآز
ظآزI'm unbreakableظآز
ظآزWhat destiny brought us to meetظآز
ظآزTwo different worlds, a love so sweetظآز
ظآزA wish we made
in a past life, it seemsظآز
ظآزDestined to cross time and dream ظآز
ظآزLike a fairytale story toldظآز
ظآزA gentle breeze feels so boldظآز
ظآزAs your hair brushes past your earظآز
ظآزI long to kiss your cheek, my dearظآز
ظآزAll my longing, all my love for youظآز
ظآزHas never changed, it's forever trueظآز
ظآزIt's the hand of fate
that we meet againظآز
ظآزLet me hold you once againظآز
ظآزResting against your chestظآز
ظآزYour warmth shines like stars at nightظآز
ظآزLet me kiss you once againظآز
ظآزNo reason neededظآز
ظآزMy heart belongs to youظآز
ظآزI'm not afraid
to cross time to find youظآز